# Victoria Bonk

Experience Designer & Strategist

719.244.0382

J

victoriabonk@gmail.com



victoriabonk.com



linkedin.com/in/victoria-bonk/



Denver, CO



## EDUCATION

Certificate – UX/UI Design University of Denver 2021

Master of Arts – Exhibition Design George Washington University 2016

Bachelor of Art – Graphic Design Marymount University 2013

## SOFTWARE

Figma

Invision

Visual Studio Code

Adobe XD

Studio 3D Max

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Indesign

Microsoft Word

Microsoft PowerPoint

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Freelance experience designer & strategist. Specializing in creating strong, appealing visuals, and environments that generate full, immersive, memorable experiences. Leads creatively to ensure that experience touchpoints resonate back to branding and the message is visually communicated within a multi-dimensional experience. From big ideas to fine print, I ensure that every detail of every touchpoint is engaging and connected.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **Experience Strategist**

Storycraft Lab | Contract / Remote | September 2020 - Present

Work with clients to design and strategize the attendee experience for their virtual events.

- Designs event webpages and supplies all files for development.
- Creates all graphic needs from registration emails to page banners to virtual photobooth backgrounds and frames.
- Produces videos to help the attendees navigate the platform and event to ensure a memorable experience.

## **Freelance Virtual Event & Graphic Designer**

May 2016 – Present

Freelance designer working to support my client's event needs ranging from graphic design to UX/UI design.

 Works with clients to develop and provide digital and print graphic content.

## **Lead Exhibit Designer**

Czarnowski | Denver, CO | February 2019 – August 2020

Team lead of the rental design office.

- Designed and rendered custom and rental tradeshow booths for clients in a wide range of industries.
- Led and assigned projects to a team of three designers to meet the design requests from sales executives.
- Managed the team's schedule and led meetings to support all designers, sales executives, project managers, and client needs through the design, estimate, and build process.

# Skills

UX/UI Design

Wireframing

Prototyping

Web Design

Graphic Design

HTML

CSS

Javascript / J-Query

3D Design

Video Production

Photography

Storytelling

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE CONTINUED...

# **Retail Designer**

Iron Mountains | Contract / Remote | October 2017 - May 2020

Created 3D designs for retail displays of baby car seats and strollers.

- Worked with the client to design, render, and consult on retail displays for UK-based baby product brand.
- Designed, rendered, and consulted on the client's office spaces.

## **Exhibit Designer**

PG Exhibits | Denver, CO | January 2018 - February 2019

Created 3D designs for tradeshow booths.

- Designed and rendered custom and rental tradeshow booths for clients in a wide range of industries.
- Worked with project managers to select appropriate materials and finishes for proper application and client's brand standards.

# **Event / Exhibit Designer**

Hargrove Inc. | Lanham, MD | October 2014 - May 2016

Created 3D designs for large scale events and tradeshows.

- Designed and rendered custom event designs for clients in a wide range of industries.
- Worked with estimators and project managers to select appropriate materials for event finishes, drapery, florals, and lighting.

# **Visual Information Specialist**

U.S. Botanic Garden | Washington, DC | June 2013 – October 2014 Responsible for all digital and print graphic collateral.

- Designed and maintained all permanent and temporary exhibition signage and supporting print and digital content.
- Performed content management for the museum's public-facing website. Including photographing and updating all website imagery.
- Supported the visitor services office during peak seasons.

#### **Public Affairs Specialist / Photographer**

U.S. Coast Guard | Washington, DC | August 2006 - June 2011

Servicemember with a job specialty in public affairs and photojournalism.

- Senior editor for the Service's flagship publication, *the Coast Guard Magazine*.
- Photographer for the Coast Guard Commandant.
- Incident Command System trained.
- Deployed to incidents to work with local and national media and document for the Coast Guard archives.